Guide to the Edward G. and Hortense R. Levy Autograph Collection, Part One
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Alphabetical Files, 1710-1955; 21.07; (65 boxes)
  - Young, Charles George, Sir, 1795-1869, 1835-56 (Box 65, Folder 2368)
  - Zeitter, John Christian, d. 1862, 1835 (Box 65, Folder 2369)
  - Zerffi, George Gustavus, 1821-1892, 1875 (Box 65, Folder 2370)
  - Zimmerman, Agnes, 1847-1925, 1891 (Box 65, Folder 2371)
  - Zimmerman, Henry, b. 1851, 1874-76 (Box 65, Folder 2372)